canadianappliance.ca 2016-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Canadian Appliance

The personal information that you provide in the course of your relationship with us is collected for the purpose of providing you the requested services. Your personal information will not be used for any other purpose, except with your consent, or as required by law. Your personal information will not be shared or disclosed to any other person or organization, except as may be necessary to provide the services to you and only to those who need to know that information or as otherwise authorized by you, where required by law or where necessary to take precautions against liability. We take appropriate security and other measures to preserve the confidentiality of your personal information and to ensure that it is used for the intended purposes. We will only retain your personal information for as long as is necessary for the fulfillment of purpose(s) for which the information was provided. In the event that we are acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, or if we sell a part of our business, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the personal information that we have collected from you as part of such merger, sale or other change of control. If you wish to obtain access to your personal information, please contact us at the address, phone number or email listed above. By supplying your personal information to us or using our services, you are indicating that you consent to the terms of this policy.

**Return Policy**

Our goal is to make our customers fully satisfied with the products and services we offer. We ask that customers verify the products they are ordering before finalizing an order.

Some of the features that should be verified: 

  * Gas or Electric.
  * 110 Volts or 220 Volts. 
  * Color of unit.
  * Height, Width, and Depth, will match the place where your installing the unit.
  * Height, Width, and Depth, will allow unit to fit through the entrance door.

We will not take back any unit(s) that were opened and/or taken out of the box. Please make sure you are ordering the correct item before placing your order. If you need assistance in ordering a product or you need technical help please call our sales staff at 1-877-374-3439 or email us at [cs@canadianappliancesource.ca](mailto:cs@canadianappliancesource.ca). If you need to return an item you must notify us within 7 days after receiving the unit. No returns will be accepted after that time period. There will be a 25% restocking fee on cancelled or unopened returned items, plus the shipping cost to you and back to us. If you need to cancel an order you must call us at 1-877-374-3439 to cancel. Do not email us any cancellations. All special orders or orders that have a postmarked day cannot be cancelled. We do not accept returns on air conditioners. All air conditioners and air conditioner accessories sales are final.

**Damages**

We do our best packaging our products to minimize damages. There are times that a unit may come damaged. It is very important to inspect the item upon delivery. If you notice any dents or punctures on the package please refuse the package or make note of it on the bill of lading and call customer service at 1-877-374-3439 for assistance or email us at [cs@canadianappliancesource.ca](mailto:cs@canadianappliancesource.ca) We will take every possible step in getting you out a new unit in a timely fashion. If the unit was accepted and signed for and there was a concealed damage, we will do everything necessary to repair the unit (if it is at all possible), or send a replacement unit and pick up the damaged unit. On occasion the unit might need minor repairs. We will send a service technician down to try and repair the unit. It may take up to 10 days for a service appointment. If the unit cannot be repaired we will send a new unit to the customer in a timely fashion.

**_Fixing errors or misprints:_** We strive to prevent errors. How we fix them depends on the error. If we find that a product description is incorrect, for example, we'll correct it.

In general, you should know that prices and availability are subject to change without notice. Errors will be corrected where discovered. Canadian Appliance Source reserves the right to revoke any stated offer and to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions, including after an order has been submitted, whether or not the order has been confirmed and your credit card charged. If your credit card has already been charged for the purchase and your order is canceled, [www.canadianappliance.ca](http://www.canadianappliance.ca/) will issue a credit to your credit card account in the amount of the charge. Individual bank policies will dictate when this amount is credited to your account.

While Canadian Appliance Source takes steps to ensure the accuracy and completeness of product and third-party services information provided, please refer to the originator of the information (e.g., the manufacturer) for complete product details.

Our Privacy Commitment

At Canadian Appliance Source we know how important it is to protect your personal information. Whether you are shopping with us online or in person we want to make every customer experience safe and secure. In keeping with that goal, we have developed this Privacy Policy to explain our practices for the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information.

This Policy applies to our retail stores, our Web Sites, and all other channels in which Canadian Appliance Source collects and uses your personal information.

Top­

What Information does Canadian Appliance Source Collect?

At Canadian Appliance Source, we collect two types of information: personal information and non-personal information. The types of information we collect depend on the nature of your interaction with us.

Personal information

· Personal information is information that can identify an individual or information about an identifiable individual. We may collect personal information such as:

· your contact information – e.g., name, postal address, telephone number, and email address;

· your personal preferences – e.g., product wish lists, language preferences, and marketing consent; and

· your transaction information – e.g., products purchased, method of payment, amount paid, and credit or debit card number.

Non-personal information

· Non-personal information does not identify you as an individual. For example:

· we may ask you for your postal code to assist us with planning our flyer distribution;

· we may collect certain non-personal data when you visit our Web Sites, such as the type of browser you are using or the referring URL; or

· we may collect and summarize customer information in a non-personal, aggregate format for statistical and research purposes. We may, for example, summarize our data to determine that a certain percentage of contest entrants are male, aged 18 to 25.

All references to “Web Sites” in this Privacy Policy mean [www.CanadianAppliance.ca](http://www.canadianappliance.ca/),, or other Canadian Appliance Source provided Web sites.

You may choose not to provide us with your personal information. However, if you make this choice we may not be able to provide you with the product, service, or information that you requested. For example, we can only offer you a Canadian Appliance Source credit card if you have provided us with certain financial information.

### Online Policy

#### **Fixing errors or misprints**

**  
** We strive to prevent errors. How we fix them depends on the error. If we find that a product description is incorrect, for example, we'll correct it.

In general, you should know that prices and availability are subject to change without notice. Errors will be corrected where discovered. Canadian Appliance Source reserves the right to revoke any stated offer and to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions, including after an order has been submitted, whether or not the order has been confirmed and your credit card charged. If your credit card has already been charged for the purchase and your order is canceled, [www.canadianappliance.ca](http://www.canadianappliance.ca/) will issue a credit to your credit card account in the amount of the charge. Individual bank policies will dictate when this amount is credited to your account.

While Canadian Appliance Source takes steps to ensure the accuracy and completeness of product and third-party services information provided, please refer to the originator of the information (e.g., the manufacturer) for complete product details.
